# Blake Stefansen



linkedin.com/in/blake-stefansen



https://bstefansen.github.io/Portfolio



bstefansen11@gmail.com

### Summary

University of Florida Honors | Geoscience Graduate with a passion for technology and the natural world. I specialize in JavaScript and have trained with GIS products, Python, SQL, MongoDB, React, Node, Express.js, HTML, CSS, Git/Github, WordPress, Microsoft Office, Google Suite, and Adobe Suite. I have a strong foundation in software and web development, graphic design, geographic information systems analysis, and the geological sciences.

Take a look at my portfolio, and let's get in touch! https://bstefansen.github.io/Portfolio/

### Experience



#### Founder

**Get Sufficient** 

May 2020 - Present (2 months +)

- Founded Get Sufficient: an online media WordPress blog about self-sufficiency and sustainability.
- Configured domain and hosting.
- Deployed custom CSS and HTML.
- Customized and configured diverse plugins and themes.

### Associate Field Geologist

TERRA-COM Environmental Consulting, Inc.

May 2019 - Jun 2019 (2 months)

- Collaborated with geologists in preparation of site assessments.
- Executed groundwater sampling field services compliant with FDEP regulations.

#### Office Assistant

#### Florida Credit Union

Jan 2016 - Apr 2019 (3 years 4 months)

- Launched first annual cost analysis report of office supplies, informing senior management on optimizing annual savings.
- Developed and managed ordering systems and databases for company supplies through Smartsheet and Excel, streamlining ordering procedures for company branches and departments.
- Reduced vendor pricing of office supplies and supervised inventory of corporate office to enhance workflow for office personnel.
- Drafted and optimized procedures for diverse office tasks.



#### Customer Service Representative

#### Walgreens

Oct 2015 - Dec 2015 (3 months)

- Managed the front register and interacted with customers.
- Maintained receipts and answered incoming phone requests.
- Gave appropriate change, requested price checks, and rung up sales.

#### **Education**



Certificate, Geospatial Information Analysis (GIS) 2019 - 2020

## **UF** University of Florida

Bachelor's degree, Geological and Earth Sciences/Geosciences | Honors 2018 - 2020

## S<sub>F</sub> Santa Fe College

Associate of Arts - AA, Geology 2017 - 2018

#### **Licenses & Certifications**



- (A) Responsive Web Design freeCodeCamp
- (A) JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures freeCodeCamp
- (A) Front End Libraries freeCodeCamp
- (A) APIs and Microservices freeCodeCamp
- (A) Data Visualization freeCodeCamp
- (A) Information Security and Quality Assurance freeCodeCamp
- (A) Full Stack freeCodeCamp

#### **Honors & Awards**

Cum Laude | Honors - University of Florida May 2020

SF Honors Graduate - Santa Fe College

SF Charles L. Blount Scholarship - Santa Fe College

- Florida Bright Futures Scholarship The Florida Department of Education
- Florida Credit Union Scholarship Florida Credit Union 2017
- The Education Foundation Senior Scholarship Alachua County Public Schools 2017

#### Skills

JavaScript • Geographic Information Systems (GIS) • SQL • React.js • Node.js • MongoDB • Python (Programming Language) • WordPress • Express.js • Adobe Photoshop